xnepali.com 2013-11-21

# Privacy Policy | Nepali Movies, Nepali Films

* * *

## [Privacy Policy](http://xnepali.net/movies/about-2/privacy-policy/ "Permanent Link to Privacy Policy")

* * *

 **Privacy Policy**

This is the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) for the xNepali portal Web site “xnepali.com” and its sub-domains. The Site is made available by xNepali Team . This Privacy Policy sets forth our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of certain information relating to your use of the Site . Your use of this Site signifies your understanding and acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy.

 **Age Requirement for Use of Site:**  
Some page in this Site is not intended for use by underage persons. Definition of legal age depends on the law of user’s country or state . You must be legal age of your state or country to use those pages in the Site.

 **1\. Collecting Information:**  
As with many Web sites, we may use “cookies” and/or other technology in the Site or in our communications with you to enhance the functionality of the Site and to make your transactions and other activities more convenient and efficient (collectively, “Tracking Technologies”). These technologies may vary, but in some cases may involve a small file stored locally on the computer used to access the Site, and may be used by us to store and collect information relating to your viewing and use of the Site and our correspondences with you. We may collect your IP (Internet Protocol) address to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Site and identify our users. We may also use such technologies to remember user preferences or minimize the need for you to re-enter information.

Third parties (including, but not limited to, software vendors, advertisers, content providers and fulfillment companies) may also use Tracking Technologies by or through the Site. We have no control over what information such third parties track or collect, and we have no responsibility or liability for any tracking, data collection or other activities of such third parties.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:

http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

http://chitika.com/privacy_policy.php

 **2\. Usage and Sharing:**  
We reserve the right to disclose any information concerning you if required by law or to protect or defend our rights or the rights or well-being of our users or if you are involved (or are reasonably suspected to be involved) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order.

 **3\. Posting Information on or Through the Site:**  
You are solely responsible for the information and other content you post on or through the Site. You understand that personal and other information (e.g., user name, e-mail address, phone number) that you post on or through the Site (e.g., chat, bulletin boards) as well as your general communications with the Site are generally accessible to, and may be collected and used by, others and may result in unsolicited messages or other contact from others. Users of the Site are encouraged to exercise caution when providing personal information about them selves. In the event that you submit personal information regarding a third party to us via the Site (e.g., via a “refer a friend” feature) or otherwise, you hereby warrant and represent that such third party has consented to your doing so, for use in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **4\. Security:**  
Due to the open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any information stored on our servers, or transmitted to or from a user, will be free from unauthorized access. By using the Site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.

 **5\. Consent to Processing:**  
By providing any personal information to this Site, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the transfer of such personal information to, and the collection and processing of such personal information in,  Nepal and other countries or territories.

 **6\. Links:**  
This Site may contain links or references to other Web sites outside of our control. Please be aware that we have no control over these sites and our privacy policy does not apply to these sites.

 **7\. Your Acceptance of this Policy:**  
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time so visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us by sending email to blog[at]xnepali.com .
